<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BookDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<bookDescList>
		<BookDesc BookID="17000001">
			<BookName>The Black Silence</BookName>
			<TextList>
 				<Desc>I could put up with it all just for this moment…
I’ve come this far so I can make her suffer the same… No, to bring her even more pain than what I’ve suffered.</Desc>
				<Desc>I don’t exactly believe there’s happiness waiting for me at the end of this…
There’d only be empty regret. I’d get nothing out of it.</Desc>
				<Desc>But that’s still better than suffocating under these emotions that couldn’t be let out, isn’t it?
I just want to be able to breathe for a second.</Desc>
				<Desc>You’ve got your causes to fight for. Don’t hold back.
Few things could be more agonizing and detestable than finding a common ground between each other’s goals.</Desc>
				<Desc>Angela. Your pain and loss will be much greater than mine…
…Alright. Let’s get started.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="17000002">
			<BookName>The Putrid Giant</BookName>
			<TextList>
 				<Desc>The past isn’t all that different from now… Nothing ever changes… The same kinds of tragedies happen time and time again…
Everyone knows that it’s wrong… But they can’t stop it from repeating…
How many people do you think are sacrificed for the convenience and happiness of others…?</Desc>
				<Desc>The City’s prosperity is fueled by the lives of others… And its people stick their heads below the parapet and carry on…
There’s no other way to survive in this damned place…
We all know that it’s pointless to reflect on ourselves and think things over…</Desc>
				<Desc>You wouldn’t want to care… You’d want to turn a blind eye!
Because that’s none of your business… Right. That’s none of your business.
Because your life would be a bit more comfortable if you just closed your eyes and turned away…</Desc>
				<Desc>They give no ear to the pain of other people… Taking care of themselves is already hard enough…
I hate this City for forcing us to be like this…
And I’m horrified and disgusted at myself for partaking in its filthy business…</Desc>
				<Desc>But—that’s that, and this is this…
I can’t just sit and watch as my happiness goes down the drain…
My life is far from a clean one, but still… I hadn’t done anything to earn anyone’s grudge…</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="17000003">
			<BookName>The Black Servant</BookName>
			<TextList>
 				<Desc>What I cannot do is own her heart.
Instead, my graceful love stole my heart and left me with lone hardship.
I can’t help but love the pain which fills the void of solitude.</Desc>
				<Desc>Because I could look ahead thanks to you.
But now, the wonderful scenery we used to watch together lay behind me…
In this instant, I look back again. My eyes fixated on the most painful yet beautiful moments.</Desc>
				<Desc>Those moments I can only view from afar, as I can’t dare approach them.
As I cleared the filth obstructing my view, it piled up on the path to the way forward…
I don’t think I can face the growing mountain in front of me squarely.</Desc>
				<Desc>If I tried to confront it…
I might be buried under mounds of resentment and suffering from others.
I’m not sad about it, though. I don’t think it’s a shame that I can’t move on.</Desc>
				<Desc>To leave you behind in the past and move forward alone would be my greatest pain.
I had only one option, then. To be able to gaze at paradise forever…
I should move all which blocks that sight out of the way.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="17000103">
			<BookName>The White Guard</BookName>
			<TextList>
 				<Desc>Look
One by one
The pages remind me you'll always be a villain
For you,angels have fallen
Now they're gone
See? Now they're gone
Forever gone
From the hell that served as my one and only home
Though it may hurt today
Tomorrow I'll be heading my way</Desc>
				<Desc>I tried, I tried
What did we expect?
My dearest friend
Tell me when we shall make it end</Desc>
				<Desc>So let me take your hand
Like one of those madmen
Tip tappity tappity tap
Dance our last dance
Sing
Ta talila lulilatu
Spinning vinyl opera
(Lascia ch'io pianga) Longing for this moment
(mia cruda sorte,)Brewing all this hatred
(e che sospiri) So I have a reason
(la libertà.) Reason to see you dead</Desc>
				<Desc>Don't you worry
I saved a spot for you in recycle bin
Your neighbouring addresses point to the books you burned</Desc>
				<Desc>Stop now, One by one
Your desires convince me you've always been a human
For you, the shelves have fallen
Now they're gone
See? Now they're gone
Forever gone
From the stage that allowed us our one and only dreams
What's more to say?
Pain always catches up to those who chooses to stay
Though it may hurt today
Tomorrow I'll be heading my way</Desc>
			</TextList>
		</BookDesc>
	<BookDesc BookID="17000004">
			<BookName>The Lunatic</BookName>
			<TextList>
 				<Desc>If I beheaded my nightmare, I might feel good for a moment.
I had been bearing with this shit until now to experience this small victory…
If I were to gouge out this pain, would I be able to accept that it’s over?</Desc>
				<Desc>If I neglected this choice I’ve been given, wouldn’t it… find a way to me in some other form eventually?
I thought it’d all be over once I could accomplish this dream of vengeance.
I had a reason I couldn’t give up… I told myself that this was for me…</Desc>
				<Desc>That it’s only fair for me to destroy this place for taking the one I cherished away.
Even if no one understood me… At least I would be able to understand myself.
Deeper into the darkest depths. Fate made my heart cruel.</Desc>
				<Desc>The paradise I only got to step in once… What did I do for it to be stolen from me so ruthlessly?
Time stood still for me ever since that day. All I can see now is the life of the past, shrouded in darkness.
But if I forgave everything…</Desc>
				<Desc>If I decided to live down my past now, I felt I might have nowhere to stand.
And I felt I might have to let go of all these precious memories of it.
That’s what really scares me, Angelica.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
	<BookDesc BookID="17000005">
			<BookName>The Gone Angels</BookName>
			<TextList>
				<Desc>It’s been a while, Roland… I was waiting for you to show up. So you’ve been guarding this monster mimicking a human all along?
Roland… Is this what your big plan was all about? Is this really worth it?
What you’re doing isn’t any different from all the tragedies we’ve seen and gone through… You’ve been perpetuating it in the Library with that machine.</Desc>
				<Desc>……</Desc>
				<Desc>I’m partly responsible for what happened to you, which led you here…
You have no idea the mess I had to clean up after you went missing.
Neither of us had parents or any real family, so you probably thought no one would be concerned about you.
And you were wrong. I was actually pretty worried for you, unlike some others in Charles’ Office.
A bunch of thoughts came to my mind when you left after making a lengthy ramble.</Desc>
				<Desc>……</Desc>
				<Desc>None of that would have happened if you hadn’t tried to take a sip of the sauce out of the ladle “to see how great its taste must be to cause an incident”.
…Those were the days, still. We didn’t have to worry about too many things, and just stuck to the matters at hand.
Yeah… But you know we can’t go back to those times anymore, Roland.</Desc>
				<Desc>……</Desc>
				<Desc>You swallowed your anger and sadness to work with that machine, so I don’t doubt that you’ve prepared yourself for a lot of things.
That’s that, and this is this. Isn’t that right?</Desc>
				<Desc>……</Desc>
				<Desc>…Right you are. That’s that, and this is this.</Desc>
				<Desc></Desc>
				<Desc>……</Desc>
 				<Desc>Hahaha… Do you think I’m like you? You might have seen through one thing, but you can’t see further than that.
I’m not planning to return my suffering in full.
But, it took no time for those feelings to dissipate into nothing.
Was it truly a tragedy that I lost her? Who defined it as tragedy?
Roland, you may still be blinded by wrath, but I made the decision that I will care not about those feelings anymore.</Desc>
				<Desc>……</Desc>
				<Desc>That’s not it, Roland… I’m going to send off Angelica with this performance.
I won’t be going on an unsightly rampage, unlike a certain someone.
That Angelica can justify the pursuit of an ambition tainted by unclean desires is just a dreadful excuse now.</Desc>
				<Desc>……</Desc>
				<Desc>Haha. You’re still keeping those gloves…… How putrid.</Desc>	
				<Desc>……</Desc>
				<Desc>…Shut up.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
	</bookDescList>
</BookDescRoot>