<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BookDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<bookDescList>
		<BookDesc BookID="18000000">
			<BookName>Conductor Argalia's Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
        		<Desc>When I heard the news and rushed to the scene, only a hideous musician who had concluded his performance and permanently shut the piano’s lid with his torso awaited me. For the first time, emotions I couldn’t understand welled up inside me. It’s hard to define what they were, even now. It felt as if deep tenebrous stains were seeping out of my heart. Alas, I didn’t shed tears before that piano where your body rested—for I soon realized that you were no longer there.</Desc>
        		<Desc>That’s right; you’re the gentle breeze that brushes past my face, and the clouds that fly in the sky, which give me heed of your presence from overhead or underfoot. I thought you had left me, but you would always come back. That’s why I care no longer about the skin and flesh you wore only momentarily. Angelica. I’ll follow after the name you gave me: Uberto. You used to call me that down in those horrible underground chambers. I’ll create a new world… one where people can live bountiful lives even if they have nothing, free from obsession or greed. When we lose the fixation on our bodies, we won’t be afraid of death anymore. No rest will be eternal.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18100000">
			<BookName>Philip's Sonorous Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
        		<Desc>How much longer must I walk until I reach an end? How tightly must I shut my eyes, cover my ears, and zip my mouth to keep what’s around me safe before I can feel a semblance of happiness that won’t leave me? I thought I had to overcome this pain and rise above it to become a tougher man. That way, I wouldn’t lose those that are close to me. However, a human is fragile by nature; if one is too weak, they would crumble—and if one is too hardy, they would snap. I realized that there’s little I can do to calm the disorder of this world. How can I live on without falling to despair, then? A mind that is willing to let go of things that were destined to leave at some point. A mind that is content to have nothing. I feel that it’s important to refrain from thinking that anything is in my possession.</Desc>
        		<Desc>I followed your troupe in order to find a way to be happy, but what good did it do for me? Staying with you only exacerbated my suffering, defeating the whole purpose of joining you in the first place. I do want to add that you were not at fault here, though. I was the one who tormented myself. Had I known what I know now back in the past… would that have lessened the pain or changed anything? No, I don’t blame myself for the choice in that moment. Even the failures and misery of the past were all part of the voyage leading up to this moment, so I’m thankful that I managed to achieve something for once. I might have drowned in my own tears and sorrow back then, but ultimately, I’m grateful for the choice I made… and all the things in the world.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18200000">
			<BookName>Eileen's Glittering Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
				<Desc>Where we live, there is nothing that can be achieved with your own will. A flow that we cannot go against dictates us. What we call “gears” are simply there to show the flow. You can’t see it with your eyes. Nobody knows who created this massive current, or why we must follow it. This flow never leads us to bad places, however. Rather, thinking that such a place exists is an act of defiance in itself.</Desc>
        		<Desc>We merely watch events unfold as bystanders. You walk along a path, but was it you who laid the path there? You didn’t teach yourself to lift your legs to propel you forward; they simply moved. Furthermore, the decision to walk wasn’t our own, either. Still too many believe that they moved their legs out of their own volition. It’s a shame to see them struggle to escape the flow, for they’re only straying away from salvation.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18210000">
			<BookName>Gear Worshippers' Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
				<Desc>Why we have to use Smiling Faces' Smoke.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18300000">
			<BookName>Greta’s Confident Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
 				<Desc>It’s an era where humans are dominated by the act of consumption! When you’re hungry you get annoyed, and when starvation touches your raw nerve, you turn violent. That’s how humans are. And people who eat the same food will naturally grow similar. So the high and mighty beings that wanna rule over you demand ya to eat the “correct” stuff! When something’s “correct”, there’s gotta be something that’s “incorrect”. Incorrect food. It’s gotta mean humans eating humans, don’tcha think?</Desc>
        		<Desc>Why do people think that eating is natural, but then draw the line at eating their fellow man? Who decided it so, and why! Is it because human life is precious? That’s a flawed statement! What makes the lives of animals less precious? We’re not aboutta go down a boring philosophical riddle about the weight of life, now. If humans clearly have more value over animals ‘cause we’re the apex predators, then there shouldn’t be any problem with a pack of humans that rise above the rest and prey on others.</Desc>
        		<Desc>We’ve got two options! First: don’t eat anything. Hey, I’m not suggesting that we all starve to death. Your body is taught to eat! So what if you changed that habit? Maybe instead of food, your empty innards could be filled with possibilities of some other kind? If you ain’t a fan of that, then there’s the second option: eat anything! Just trace the smell of the blood, and stuff what you find in your mouth as your brain tells you to.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
    	<BookDesc BookID="18400000">
      		<BookName>The Page of Heehaw, Woof and Doodle-doo</BookName>
      		<TextList>
        		<Desc>Let’s go on an adventure—a world that changes with every step. The me that changes after each step I take. My eyes dazzled by colorful light, I pursue pleasures that I don’t have. Don’t scold us because you can’t understand our pursuit. You just happen to be one of the many who feel joy from common things. We—on the other hand—don’t see any colors in those. You’re the ones drenched in nasty pleasures. We’re simply looking for what we lack. But complete satisfaction will never come; it’ll only sink deeper in the raging thirst. We will spend our days in yet grander debauchery. We’re happy, though. We can wet ourselves in new colors every day, unlike the rest of you.</Desc>
      		</TextList>
    	</BookDesc>
    	<BookDesc BookID="18500000">
      		<BookName>Oswald's carecessing Page</BookName>
      		<TextList>
        		<Desc>People have hopes and dreams!
“I wanna eat three blossoms of flowers!”
“I wanna be a swifty nifty thrifty kitty!”
“I wanna earn a fortune!”
And then they add:
“Maybe I’ll find delicious flowers someday!”
“Maybe I’ll get fat stacks of cash in my paws someday!”
“Maybe I’ll be showered in the loudest applause someday!”
“Someday! Someday! Someday!”
That dastardly “someday” just won’t stop popping up. But to have a hope, you’ve got to prepare incense to offer those wishful prayers upon. A world where one can’t eat flowers! A reminder that you’re a sluggish turtle right now! The beggarly reality! Setting the stage for the performance we call hope!</Desc>
        <Desc>Thus and therefore, people have the wrong idea about how to have hopes! If they believe that the hopes will come true “someday”, they’ll just keep parroting that contemptible word! The day will never actually come! Having expectations this way will only leave you with bitter anger!
“I’ll change someday?”
“That person will turn over a new leaf someday, if I count on them and wait?”
Nyeh, tch.
People entertain the hopes as they please, and then bite at each other when the change they expected doesn’t happen. Clowns can’t give out smiles in a world full of mean teary friends!</Desc>
        <Desc>So we should all do the stretches, starting today! Abandon all expectation—just keep a merry positive attitude and laugh no matter what you see! Let’s make a performance about what’s already come true, not of a supposed reality you hope for “someday”! I’m already on the stage, standing under the brightingest spotlight ever.</Desc>
      		</TextList>
    	</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18510000">
			<BookName>Mr Knife's Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
      			<Desc></Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18520000">
			<BookName>Ms Mermaid's Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
      			<Desc></Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18600000">
      		<BookName>Tanya’s lively Page</BookName>
      		<TextList>
        		<Desc>Fighting for survival is a natural thing. Even now, we’re all in battle. There’re more people born than folks dying of natural causes, and the living struggle in their own positions every day. A fight to protect, and to avoid falling behind. Maybe it’s all ‘cause there just ain’t enough seats for the ever-growing population of humans to take? Sure, extra jobs and stuff could be made in the future, but that’s nothing more than a hopeful estimate that might not happen until it’s too late for you. The world we live in right now is what matters. There’s got to be a way to weed out the unfit without straining all of us. And that’s when strength plays its part.</Desc>
        		<Desc>I don’t get why you vilify this. Aren’t we all doing the same thing, directly or not? We elbow our way past others so we can survive, and the losers are knocked outta the race. You say this is fair, but say no to physical conflicts, to “respect life” or whatevs? Then lemme ask: what’s the reason to respect life? Do you think you’re respecting life right now?</Desc>
      			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18700000">
			<BookName>Jae-heon's Eloquent Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
    			<Desc>Had I been busy with an urgent appointment as any other tragic tale should go, your death wouldn’t have felt so miserable. Yeah. I would’ve cried until my tears had run their course, and I would’ve been ready to send you off. It was an ordinary day. The sort of day when there were no meetings or gatherings to attend to after I came home from work. Your body was crushed beyond recognition—I couldn’t have noticed on my own that it wasn’t a random chunk of flesh. They put your remains in a stasis box and sent it to me; that was their gesture of condolence. I’d have refused to believe it was you, if it weren’t for the clothes. I spent hours sitting there in numbed silence, vacantly staring at a lump I couldn’t even dare to hug.</Desc>
        		<Desc>A stuffed doll you were carrying, now next to the box, caught my eye. Even though it was shredded and soaked in blood, the cotton filling was still clustered together, as if it remembered the volume of the doll. It seems some cotton remained even after the roller crumpled all the outer fabric. Then for reasons unknown, I brought the other dolls out of your room and cut them up with a pair of scissors. I don’t know what possessed me to cut them into pieces of fabric. There wasn’t even enough to fully cover the doll, so I scraped together the pieces of clothing to sew it back up. With the same, gentle hands that made your doll the first time.</Desc>
        		<Desc>The outcome was creepier than what it used to be, but it was the same doll I remembered nonetheless. The appearance didn’t matter. Maybe, just maybe, the same could be said for you? I gazed at the box where you, my son, rested for what would no longer be an eternity. My two hands were once so busy that it was a bother; they had paused for the time, but now they are about to move again—just for you.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18710000">
			<BookName>Puppet Angelica’s Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
				<Desc>Gigigigigig</Desc>
				<Desc>Ghghghghghghghgh…</Desc>
				<Desc>Creeeeak…</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18800000">
			<BookName>Elena's Sensuous Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
      			<Desc>Bloodfiends. The beings said to have been punished with neverending thirst for the sin of lusting after human blood. That’s what your kind called us, condemning us out of fear. I was afraid as well when I faced them for the first time in that mansion where everything began. Violent beings who drank the blood of fellow humans. A growing feeling of unease about the possibility of being their next target. The people in the mansion were terrified of those who became monsters. Even though they were humans like us, they were outside of what we thought as the norm. In hindsight, though, it was such a silly thing to do. What is the illusion of normalcy that we feared for and fought for so strongly?</Desc>
        		<Desc>Let’s say that every human on the planet except for one turned into Bloodfiends, and that single person remaining is left “normal”, as they say. In that case, what would normalcy be like there? How must the lone human feel being the monster among the creatures they dreaded? Should they fight to their last breath for the “humanity” they kept for so long? Perhaps that’s become an obsolete ideology, one that’s no longer worth keeping. What if rejecting that old ideal and becoming a Bloodfiend opened up our potential for growth in numerous aspects?</Desc>
        		<Desc>Your kind likes to claim that something is out of the ordinary when it’s only different from what you’ve seen and experienced before. So you fear it, and try to exclude it from your herd. But you see, there’s no real justification for your kind to condemn us.</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18810000">
			<BookName>The Dim Vermilion's Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
      			<Desc></Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
		<BookDesc BookID="18900000">
			<BookName>Pluto's Solemn Page</BookName>
			<TextList>
 				 <Desc>The world is one massive aggregation of delusions. A world where individuals can shape their own reality as they see fit. Every person is susceptible to deception, for they have knowledge. For that reason, it is impossible for a pure being untainted by knowledge to see the world as we mistakenly observe it, in the same way they cannot discern the end point of a line or tell between blue and red. A world devoid of wants. It would be unfit to call that place a world. In fact, to even call it a “place” would be yet another misconception amongst us knowing ones. The more one learns, the more delusions they invite.</Desc>
        		<Desc>However, if most people observed the same place and felt the same sentiments, then it might not be your own delusion after all. Wouldn’t you say so? For instance, take a look at the blue sky. The celestial dome is higher and farther than one can fathom, and as blue as it can be. Most will agree that the sky is tall and blue. Alas, those who think as such are ultimately within your view. It’s only natural that they agree with you as they’re figments born out of your delusional mind. Indeed, the sly entity that prevents you from seeing the world in its sincerest form would be none other than yourself. Even the holy entity in which you believe and to which you devote yourself is going to be a projection of your own self, so how can I trust anything that my eyes show me?</Desc>
			</TextList>
			<PassiveList />
		</BookDesc>
	</bookDescList>
</BookDescRoot>