<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <!--General-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1900001">
        <Name>Speed</Name>
        <Desc>Speed Dice Slot +1. Gain a Speed die on the third Scene. 
Gain an additional die if there's an enemy whose Emotion Level is 4 or higher.
Does not gain Speed dice from Emotion Level bonuses.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1900000">
        <Name>Perfect Extraction -- Prime Soul</Name>
        <Desc>The Deck Limit is increased to 18. Additional Pages will not be added to a deck with 9 or more Pages.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--总指挥家-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1900002">
        <Name>Conducting the final chapter</Name>
        <Desc>Every 3 Scenes, all allies gain 1 "Emozioni Intensificantesi" (At the start of each Scene, gain 1 Strength and Endurance).
Upon death, all allies are inflicted with "disarray" (Uncontrollable; targets random characters including allies; When attacking ally deal 50% more Stagger Damage; This status lasts 3 Scenes)</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1900003">
        <Name>Synphony No. 5</Name>
        <Desc>At the start of each act add a copy of "Tempestuous Danza" to hand. Activating "Resonance" 3 times will increase the natural roll of the Page by +1.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--哭泣之子-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1910001">
        <Name>Borrowed Embers</Name>
        <Desc>While alive, the first Offensive die allies play each engagement inflicts 2 Burn on hit.
After death, allies are inflicted with 1 Burn when hit.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1910002">
        <Name>Superheat</Name>
        <Desc>If there is a total 30 stacks Burn on the field at the start of Scene, Dice gain +1 Power and inflict +25% more Damage and Stagger Damage for the duration of that Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1910003">
        <Name>Restraints</Name>
        <Desc>Upon winning 6 clashes against the same target in a single scene, inflict 1 'Restraint' at the end of the Scene.
Upon hitting a target with 3 or more stacks of 'Restraint', Immobilize them for the next Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--齿轮教团-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1920001">
        <Name>Prognosis</Name>
        <Desc>While alive, allies gain the effect of 'Puffy Brume'. Upon death, allies are inflicted with 10 Smoke and lose the effect of 'Puffy Brume'.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1920002">
        <Name>Fumigating Smoke</Name>
        <Desc>Every Scene, all allies gain Smoke equal to half the amount of Smoke this character has.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1920003">
        <Name>Foggy Matrix</Name>
        <Desc>If the character has 'Smoke', Reduce incoming Damage by (5 * Smoke)%;
At the end of each Scene, if the character has 10 stacks of Smoke, draw 1 Page and recover 1 Light</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--八大主厨-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1930001">
        <Name>Knight in Shark Fins</Name>
        <Desc>While alive, all other allies gain 2 Protection and Stagger Protection. Upon death, all allies are inflicted with 5 Fragile next Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1930002">
        <Name>Add Salt to Injury</Name>
        <Desc>If the target has 5 or more Bleed, Inflict 1 Fragile on hit. (Max. 3)</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1930003">
        <Name>Dermal Regeneration</Name>
        <Desc>If the character was not hit by any attacks for a Scene, recover 15 HP and gain 1 Strength Endurance.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--不来梅乐团-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1940001">
        <Name>Martial Song of the Battlefield</Name>
        <Desc>While this character is alive, give a random ally one stack of a status effect. (Strength, Endurance, or Haste) for each Light this character has.
Upon death: all enemies gain 3 Strength, Endurance, and Haste next scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1940002">
        <Name>Beklemmt Resolve</Name>
        <Desc>Cost of all pages is reduced by 2. Can only recover 1 Light at the start of each Scene. Loses all Light when Staggered.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--八点档马戏团-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1950001">
        <Name>Showtime~</Name>
        <Desc>At the end of the Scene, all enemies take Stagger damage euqal to 3-6% of Max Stagger Resist.
Upon death, all enemies fully restore Stagger Resist, and all status ailments on them are halved.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1950002">
        <Name>I Can Shrug That Off!</Name>
        <Desc>Cannot lose more than 50% of Max HP in a single Scene. Whenever an ally dies, takes 16 Stagger damage.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1950003">
        <Name>Intermission</Name>
        <Desc>Gain a copy of "Intermission Time~", making self disappear from the battlefield for 2 Scene. Recover all Lights and draw 6 Pages when returned. 
If staggered when disappeared, then reappear immediately.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1950004">
        <Name>Fusion with Red String</Name>
        <Desc>If there is an allied and alive Puppeteer present, gain the ability to use "Strangle with Red String".
an [On Play] page that forces the Puppeteer to use "Red String Conjoins" on enemies, making them gain 2 "Red Strings" next Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1950101">
        <Name>Amalgamation</Name>
        <Desc>If spawned by the effects of 'Red Strings', Max HP increases by hp lost from character that was conjoined, and gains some passive abilities of the enemies conjoined.
At the start of each Scene, draw 2 Pages.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--狼之时刻-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1960001">
        <Name>Fierce Sandstorm</Name>
        <Desc>At the end of the Scene, all enemies take damage equal to 3-6% Max HP.
After death, all enemies deal +3 damage with attacks for the rest of the Act.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1960002">
        <Name>Burning Resolve to Fight On</Name>
        <Desc>If there are no other allies present at the end of the Scene, gain 1 Strength and Endurance, and gain 2 Speed dice for the rest of the Act.
At the start of each Scene, draw 2 Pages and recover 2 Light.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1960003">
        <Name>Lord and Clown</Name>
        <Desc>If there is an allied and alive 8 O'clock Circus presnet, reduce incoming Stagger Damage by 30%.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--傀儡师-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1970001">
        <Name>Entangled Strings</Name>
        <Desc>When a die each ally plays rolls the minimum value, reroll it. Activates once per die. At the start of the Scene, all enemies are inflicted with 1-3 Bind.
After death, all enemies gain 1-3 Haste at the start of each Scene, and all of their dice gain +1 Power for the rest of the Act.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1970002">
        <Name>Sandstorm Entanglement</Name>
        <Desc>If there is an allied and alive L’heure du Loup presnet, successful hits will inflict 1 Bleed next Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1970003">
        <Name>Unbound Flesh</Name>
        <Desc>A successful kill will randomly summon an uncontrollable Puppet, Nimble Puppet or Weighty Puppet</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--猩红之月-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1980001">
        <Name>Blood is Fuel</Name>
        <Desc>All allies recover 2 health on hit. On Death, all allies lose 50% Max HP</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1980002">
        <Name>Vampiric Rampage</Name>
        <Desc>For each 40 health recoverd in a single Act, Dice gain +1 power.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1980003">
        <Name>Unwielding Will</Name>
        <Desc>Revive next Scene after first death.
Revived body only has the passive "Speed" and stats of 100/50 with 2-6 speed dice.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--昨日之约-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1990001">
        <Name>Unjust Exploitation</Name>
        <Desc>Can use Pages that inflict "Unjust Contract" on enemies. 
On Death, exhaust all Pages in hands of all allies.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1990002">
        <Name>Stygian Shade</Name>
        <Desc>Gain a copy of "Hex: Shade Eclipse" that spawns a Shade that copies target's Combat Pages and passives.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1990011">
        <Name>Without Light</Name>
        <Desc>If Yesterday's Promise is not present at the end of the Scene, die.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1990012">
        <Name>Powerful Shadow</Name>
        <Desc>Dice Power +1. Can use one of the Shade's Combat Page every Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
</PassiveDescRoot>