<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<!--奖励通用-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1800000">
		<Name>Perfect Extraction: Reverberation Ensemble</Name> 
		<Desc>Gain bonus according to present Reverberation Ensemble member.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--阿尔加利亚-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1800001">
		<Name>Perfect Resonance</Name> 
		<Desc>Whenever "Resonance" is activated, recover 2 Light and draw 1 cards.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1800002">
		<Name>The Requiem</Name> 
		<Desc>At the start of each act add a copy of "Tempestuous Danza" to hand. Activating "Resonance" 5 times will upgrade the card.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1800003">
		<Name>Frantic Performance</Name> 
		<Desc>Gain 1 Insanity after inflicting or recieving damage equal to 2% of Max HP. Can spend Insanity to use powerful Combat Pages.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--菲利普 -->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1810001">
		<Name>Tempered Passion</Name> 
		<Desc>Whenever the Emotion Level rises, inflict 3 Burn to all characters, including self.
Gain Power by half the current Emotion Level (Rounded down).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1810002">
		<Name>Searing Sword</Name> 
		<Desc>When inflicting Burn using Combat Pages, apply +1 additional stack.
If the character has 10 or more Burn at the start of the Scene, become 'Overheated' and use "Sizzling Heart" deck; otherwise, use "Cooled Heart" deck.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1810003">
		<Name>Cooled Heart</Name> 
		<Desc>Reduce damaged taken due to Burn by 10. Set resistances to 'Endured'.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1810004">
		<Name>Sizzling Heart</Name> 
		<Desc>Inflict 2 Burn to target on hit, and inflict 2 Burn to attacker when hit;
Become more vulnerable to damage when 'Overheated'.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--艾琳-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1820001">
		<Name>Meat Gear: Production</Name> 
		<Desc>At the start of the Act, Summon and Commond 2 Gear Worshipper units. Gear Worshippers will have decks from "Meat Gear" and independent stats.
Take Stagger Damage equal to 15% of Max Stagger Resist when one of the Gear Worshippers die.
Revive a Gear Worshipper after 2 scenes.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1820002">
		<Name>Thought Gear: Predict</Name> 
		<Desc>Once per Scene, respond to a one-sided attack with an Evade die [Roll: 5-10] (Not played in clashes where both characters use a Combat Page).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1820003">
		<Name>Meat Gear: Demise</Name> 
		<Desc>On the Scene after which a Gear Worshipper dies, uses the Combat Page 'Thought Gear: Brainwash'.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1820004">
		<Name>Meat Gear: Role</Name> 
		<Desc>This character can't get bonus Speed Dice from Emotion Level.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1820005">
		<Name>Zeal of the Believers</Name> 
		<Desc>Smoke' amplifies outgoing damage instead of incoming damage on this character.
Gain three special Combat Pages that can be used to benifit the user. Replenish them after all three have been used.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--格蕾塔-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1830001">
		<Name>Regenerative Cells</Name> 
		<Desc>At the start of the act, gain 10 Resilience. Every 5 Scenes, purge all status ailments on self and gain 5 Resilience.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1830002">
		<Name>Unstoppable Viciousness</Name> 
		<Desc>Gain 3 Protection each Scene. Take +3 additional damage from attacks while afflicted with Bleed.
Cannot be Staggered. When Stagger Resist falls to 0, lose 100 Hp instead and gain 1 Strength next Scene.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
  	<PassiveDesc ID="1830003">
    	<Name>Feast and Furious</Name>
   		<Desc>At the Start of the Act, add a copy of 'Into the Sack You Go!' to deck.
Use it to turn an enemy into Fresh Meat and immobolize them until the end of the next Scene. Ally attacks against Fresh Meat will yield HP recovery equal to damage dealt.
Fresh Meat change resistances to Noraml but can at most take damage equal to 10% of their Max HP and take no Stagger Damage in a scene.</Desc>
  	</PassiveDesc>
	<!-- 不来梅-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1840001">
		<Name>Triarchy</Name> 
		<Desc>Speed Dice +1。
Every Scene, one head becomes active. Each head uses different Combat Pages.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1840002">
		<Name>Uncontrollable Performance</Name> 
		<Desc>When Staggered, the Speed die that belongs to the currently active head will break, and the character will recover from Stagger next Scene.
When all heads are destroyed, recover all heads and add one copy of "Chorus at the Climax" to hand.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
  	<PassiveDesc ID="1840003">
    	<Name>Improvisation</Name>
   		<Desc>At the start of each Scene, set cost of one random card in Hand to 0. At Emotion Level 4 and higher, set cost of one extra card in hand to 0.
This Character's Maximun Light is not affected by Emotion Level, and draw 1 less card at the start of each Scene.</Desc>
  	</PassiveDesc>
  	<PassiveDesc ID="1840004">
    	<Name>Woof ruff! Doodly-doo? Heehaw~!</Name>
   		<Desc>On a successful Blunt attack, deal 1-2 bonus Stagger damage. After a successful Blunt attack, inflict 1 Fragile to a random enemy next Scene (once per Scene)</Desc>
  	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--奥斯瓦尔德-->
  	<PassiveDesc ID="1850001">
    	<Name>There’s No Time for Staggering Struts!</Name>
   		<Desc>Takes half as much Stagger damage from attacks and deflects. Take 30 Stagger Damage whenever an ally dies.</Desc>
  	</PassiveDesc>
  	<PassiveDesc ID="1850002">
    	<Name>We Could Use a Helping Hand, Actually~?</Name>
   		<Desc>Gain a copy of "We Need You, You Know~? that can only be used when there are no stupidfied allies.
At the start of the Scene: give 2 Strength, 2 Endurance, and 3 Protection to the Stupefied ally. When the ally is Staggered: take 30 Stagger damage at the end of the Scene.</Desc>
  	</PassiveDesc>
  	<PassiveDesc ID="1850003">
    	<Name>Collaborative Performance</Name>
		<Desc>Able to choose summon Mr. Knife or Ms. Mermaid. Mr. Knife and Mrs. Mermaid will use their respective decks. (Once per Act)</Desc>
  	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1850011">
    	<Name>Twas a Joy to Perform by Your Side…!</Name>
		<Desc>When this character is defeated, Oswald takes 30 Stagger damage at the end of the Scene.</Desc>
  	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--塔尼亚-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1860001">
		<Name>Brawl</Name> 
		<Desc>Gain +1 Speed Dice; This character can't get bonus Speed Dice from Emotion Levels.
Upon being targeted by a one-sided attack, use the rightmost page in hand to clash with it.
Draw 1 page every time this passive is triggered (Max 2 per Scene).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1860002">
		<Name>Time for Round Two</Name> 
		<Desc>When HP drops to 1, fully recover HP and Stagger Resist, and purge all status ailments. HP cannot reach 0 before this occurs. (Once per Reception)
Afterwards, add a copy of "Beatdown" to the deck and gain 2 Strength and Endurance for the rest of the Act.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
  	<PassiveDesc ID="1860003">
    	<Name>Hour of the Wolf</Name>
   		<Desc>At the start of the Scene, if there are enemies untargetable, purge 'Untargetable' effects and give that had those effects 3 Protection and Stagger Protection instead.</Desc>
  	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--在宪-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1870001">
		<Name>On-site Sewing</Name> 
		<Desc>Gain a copy of "On-site Sewing" that can only be used when there is a dead ally.
Use it to revive a random dead ally as Puppet Angelica and switch to "Counter form" deck. Revived ally will use deck from "Angelica Puppet"
"Counter form" deck can only equip pages with only Counter dice.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1870002">
		<Name>The Puppeteer</Name> 
		<Desc>Blunt dice Power +1. Blunt dice deal 2 bonus Stagger Damage on hit.
Increase Stagger Damage by 1 if speed is greater than 5.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1870003">
		<Name>Puppet Performance</Name> 
		<Desc>Counter dice Power +1. On Clash Lose with counter dice, Puppet Angelica takes 8 Stagger Damage.
Can use the page 'Recoonect' (3-Cost) to make Puppet Angelica regain Puppet Strings.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1870004">
		<Name>Protective Puppetry</Name> 
		<Desc>At the start of the Scene, gain Protection and Stagger Protection by the numbers of other allies.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--安洁莉卡-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1870101">
		<Name>Gigigigigig</Name> 
		<Desc>Blunt dice Power +1. Blunt dice deal 2 bonus Stagger Damage on hit.
Increase Stagger Damage by 1 if speed is greater than 5.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1870102">
		<Name>Ghghghghghghghgh…</Name> 
		<Desc>Immortal as long as Jae-heon is alive.
At the start of each Scene, gain 1 Strength, Endure, Haste if has Puppet Strings.
Can only attack enemy with Red Mark.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1870103">
		<Name>Creeeeak…</Name> 
		<Desc>Can not act if doesn't have Puppet Strings.
When staggered or Jae-heon is staggered, lose Puppet Strings status.
When Jae-heon dies, die as well.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--伊莲娜-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1880001">
		<Name>Gnawing Hunger</Name> 
		<Desc>On hit recover amount Hp equal to 2% Max HP.
Offensive Dice gain +1 Power for every 25% Max HP lost (Max 3).</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1880002">
		<Name>Feast</Name> 
		<Desc>Gain a copy of "Feast", turning enemy with 25% Max HP or less into Nameless Shell that attacks their other allies.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1880003">
		<Name>Nameless Shell</Name> 
		<Desc>Uncontrollable, attack other allies. Die when there are no other allies.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1880004">
		<Name>Blood of Bloodfiend</Name> 
		<Desc>Gain a copy of "Pure Blood", spending 25% of Max HP on play in exchange for healing half of the amount of lost HP for an ally</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--朱红十字-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1880101">
		<Name>Scorched Body / Rabid</Name> 
		<Desc>At the start of each Scene, lose HP 10% of max HP/ At the start of each Scene, draw 1 Page and recover 1 Light.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1880102">
		<Name>Heavy Weaponry / Rampage</Name> 
		<Desc>Lose 3 Speed/ one of used "Cross Blade","Shockwave","Heated Weapon" will be used again.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1880103">
		<Name>Drained Cardiovascular</Name> 
		<Desc>This character recovers twice as much health.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<!--普鲁托-->
	<PassiveDesc ID="1890001">
		<Name>Contracts</Name> 
		<Desc>Gain copy of 5 contracts. Target an ally to put it on them or target an enemy to put it on this character self.
At the start of each Scene, Draw 1 Card.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1890002">
		<Name>Yesterday's Promise</Name> 
		<Desc>There is a marked die on half of the enemies' combat pages each scene. 
Upon Clashing with a marked die, add a single-use copy of enemy's page to hand. If the Clash was won, the copy's cost is set to 0.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1890003">
		<Name>Sealing Barrier</Name> 
		<Desc>Every Scene, become immune to damage from one type of attack when not staggered.
At the start of the Act, add a copy of 'Hex: Seal' to deck.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
	<PassiveDesc ID="1890004">
		<Name>Indifference</Name> 
		<Desc>Dice from pages not in the original deck gain 1-2 Power.</Desc>
	</PassiveDesc>
</PassiveDescRoot>