<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<PassiveDescRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <!--General-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700001">
        <Name>Perfect Extraction: Roland</Name>
        <Desc>&lt;color=#FF0000&gt;Unable to utilize Emotion Card and EGO from the Library. Any attempt to apply emotion card will result in wasting said emotion card.&lt;/color&gt;
Can only be equiped by Roland.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700002">
        <Name>Perfect Extraction: Roland</Name>
        <Desc>&lt;color=#FF0000&gt;Unable to utilize Emotion Card and EGO from the Library. Any attempt to apply emotion card will result in wasting said emotion card.&lt;/color&gt;</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--P1-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700011">
        <Name>Balck Silence</Name>
        <Desc>Draw 2 additional pages at the start of the Act. Can use exclusive Page "Furioso"
All dice on every third Combat Page used gain +2 Power.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700012">
        <Name>Retaliate</Name>
        <Desc>Gain 2 dice (Slash, 4-8) at combat start.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700013">
        <Name>Clenched Grudge</Name>
        <Desc>Recover 5 Stagger Resist on hit; lose 8 Stagger Resist on clash lose.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700014">
        <Name>Perception-blocking Mask</Name>
        <Desc>A Speed die with the lowest Speed becomes untargetable.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--P2-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700021">
        <Name>The Hatching Dead</Name>
        <Desc>Whenever another characer is defeated, spawn a Smoldering Byproduct to replace it next Scene. 
At the start of each Scene, inflict 1 Suffocating Haze.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700022">
        <Name>Alien and Horrifying</Name>
        <Desc>At the start of each Act, draw 2 cards.
On clash, make enemy lose 20% of their current Stagger Resist.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700023">
        <Name>Juggernaut</Name>
        <Desc>At the start of combat of each third Scene, use an Individual Mass Attack Page targeting all other units.
(Penetrate 4-12 [On Hit] Inflict 3 Bleed in the next Scene.)</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700024">
        <Name>Wielder of Suffocating Haze</Name>
        <Desc>When attacking, if target has Suffocating Haze, deal +2 damage.
When hit, if attacker has Suffocating Haze, take 2 less damage.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--P3 roland-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700031">
        <Name>Last Dance</Name>
        <Desc>Gain Page that make other ally synchronize with "The White Guard".
Synchronization will change both decks into those focusing on Unite and gain 4 Soul Link.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700032">
        <Name>Dark Mark</Name>
        <Desc>Dice of Pages against enemy with "Dark Mark" gain 2 Power.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700033">
        <Name>Dearly Parting</Name>
        <Desc>When The White Guard die, become staggerd and increase outgoing Damage and Stagger Damage by 100% for the rest of the Act.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--P3 angelica-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1701030">
        <Name>Request Target</Name>
        <Desc>Dice of Pages against enemy with lowest HP gain 1 Power.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1701031">
        <Name>Dark Mark</Name>
        <Desc>Leave a 'Dark Mark' on the character that engaged this character last every Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1701032">
        <Name>Dearly Parting</Name>
        <Desc>When The Black Servant die, end synchronization.
Gain 2 Strength, Endurance the Scene after the end of synchronization.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--P4-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700041">
        <Name>Balck Silence</Name>
        <Desc>Draw 2 additional pages at the start of the Act. Can use exclusive Page "Furioso"
All dice on every third Combat Page used gain +2 Power.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700042">
        <Name>Memories of the Library</Name>
        <Desc>For the duration of the phase, gain unique passive abilities each Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <!--P4 Abnormality-->
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700141">
        <Name>Aspiration</Name>
        <Desc>Max HP is increased by 15%. Gain 1-2 Speed.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700142">
        <Name>Learn</Name>
        <Desc>Can Use the Combat Page 'Learn' infinitely. 
If this character's attack hits, it inflicts a 'Lies' status which changes the Costs of pages at random next Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700143">
        <Name>Nail and Hammer</Name>
        <Desc>For this Scene, successful hit will inflict one of Slash Nail, Pierce Nail and Blunt Nail according to the attack.
Perform another succesful hit with different attack in the same Scene will proc Nail's effect and remove it. Otherwise increase the stack by 1.
Slash Nail --- when proc, for each stack inflict 3 Bleed 1 Fragile next Scene.
Pierce Nail --- when proc, for each stack deal 5 Damage to the character.
Hit Nail --- when proc, for each stack deal 5 Stagger Damage to the character.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700144">
        <Name>Guilt</Name>
        <Desc>On Clash, reduce incoming Damage from attack by dice's Power.
Upon hit from an one-side attack, increase incoming Damage from attack by 2-4</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700145">
        <Name>Blizzard</Name>
        <Desc>Inflict all other characters 3 Bind.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700146">
        <Name>Pulsation</Name>
        <Desc>Speed Dice Slot -1. On hit, give 1 Strength to all allies next Scene (once per Page). 
If the character couldn't deal any damage by the end of the Scene, take 15 Stagger damage.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700147">
        <Name>Fervent Beats</Name>
        <Desc>Gain 2 Strength and Endurance, 3 Haste, and 4 Protection this Scene. 
Reduce numbers of passive abilities recieved in the next Scene.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700148">
        <Name>Sword of Frost</Name>
        <Desc>On Hit, deal 2-4 Damage and Break Damage if target's speed is lower than the character.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
    <PassiveDesc ID="1700149">
        <Name>Pale Hands</Name>
        <Desc>Perform 3 succesful hit on same character inflict additional 3-10 Break Damage this round.</Desc>
    </PassiveDesc>
</PassiveDescRoot>