<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AbnormalityCardsRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
    <Sephirah SephirahType="ETC">
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandYun">
            <Abnormality>Finn</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - Yun’s Office</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>When an ally dies, gain 1 Strength next Scene
Reduce Incoming Damage by 2.</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>I just managed to become a Grade 9, too…</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">Oh boy. It’s not all that delightful to see such a young rookie fall like that, all things considered.</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">Well, yeah, fair point. But still, it kinda feels dirty in a way.</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandZwei">
            <Abnormality>Walter</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - Zwei Association</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>Defensive Dice Power +1.
At the start of each Scene, all allies gain 1-2 Endurance.</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>I was certain that I would succeed…</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">I guess birthright matters to them the most.</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">Nothing is ever fair in this world.</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandDawn">
            <Abnormality>Salvador</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - Dawn Office</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>On a successful hit, deal +1-2 Stagger damage if the target has Burn.
On a Clash Win with Offensive dice, inclit 6 burn if the natural roll is 5 higher than enemies' natural roll.</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>There’s no need for all of us to share the same fate.</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">That gramps still hasn’t changed after so many years.</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">Not like he needs to, though…</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="3">I guess so. I gave up caring about bonds long ago…</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandLove">
            <Abnormality>Tomerry</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - Love Town</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>On hit reduce all incoming damage of same type by 2 (Max 4) for the rest of the Scene.
On one side attack, first die on the combat page gains +3 Power.</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>…I feel empty. It’s like part of me disappeared. I’m sad… I feel like crying……</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">Well… Anything can happen.</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">When the memories of hard times burst forth, you gotta embrace ‘em to the core…</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandShi">
            <Abnormality>Yujin</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - Shi Association</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>All dice gain +1 Power.
If a die's natrual roll is Max and is higher than 5, that die gains +4 Power.</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>I was so close to reaching what I want…</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">The Red Mist was powerful. Really, that’s the only way to put it. Powerful.</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">I thought, man, it surely is true that you can do whatever you want when you’re that strong.</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandLiu">
            <Abnormality>Xiao</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - Liu Association</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>On a melee hit, inflict 1 Burn and 'Force of a Wildfire', a status that lasts 2 Scenes.
When using Mass Attack pages, gain 2 Strength and Endurance next Scene.</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>I can rest without regret, knowing that you’ll find yourself not so far from me like this…</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">She didn’t break down like the other kid with the power did, at least. I was actually amazed by how unswerving her determination could be…</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">It’s weird, though. It can’t be possible to make any change with just willpower in this world. That’s not how this City works.</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandPurple">
            <Abnormality>Iori</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - The Purple Tear</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>When a die this character plays rolls the minimum value, reroll it. Activates once per die.
Types of Offensive dice on the third page change to the type the target is weakest to</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>Uh-uh, stay still, and don’t peep a word.</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">When people feel anxiety, they tend to buckle up and prepare more thoroughly for what’s to come, you see?</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">She was treated like an all-knowing sage… She might have been aware of her own future, at least.</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandHana">
            <Abnormality>Olivier</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - Hana Association</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>Boost the *minimum* roll value of all dice by +2. At Emotion Level 3 or higher, also boost the *maximum* roll value of all dice by +1.
On Clash Win, next die's *maximun* roll +2</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>Our past ties have finally led us here, Roland.</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">Thanks for everything. And…</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">…Right you are. That’s that, and this is this.</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
        <AbnormalityCard ID="RolandBlue">
            <Abnormality>Argalia</Abnormality>
            <CardName>Memory - The Blue Reverberation</CardName>
            <AbilityDesc>Take no damage from Ranged Combat Pages.
Every 3rd Scene, inflict Nullify Power to the first enemy successfully hit.</AbilityDesc>
            <FlaborText>I won’t be going on an unsightly rampage, unlike a certain someone.</FlaborText>
            <Dialogues>
                <Dialogue ID="1">Shut Up</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="2">What do you wanna hear? We both know each other’s goals.</Dialogue>
                <Dialogue ID="3">You want to crush me, the City, and most of all Angela for taking Angelica’s life.</Dialogue>
            </Dialogues>
        </AbnormalityCard>
    </Sephirah>
</AbnormalityCardsRoot>