<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<localize xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<text id="ui_ContingecyLevel">Risk Level {0} : {1}</text>
	<text id="ui_RewardStage">Congrats for completing the Risk {0} Level Challenge of {1}</text>
	<text id="ui_MoreEquipPage"> and more Keypages</text>
	<text id="ui_popup_getequippage">Gain {1} Keypage: “{0}”</text>
	<text id="ui_disable_reward">Are you sure about disabling Contract Reward Pages?
Disabling Contract Reward Pages will remove all of available Reward Pages, and will no longer provide Reward Pages aftter completing high risk level receptions. This setting is more suitable for players that only want to enjoy diffcult playthroughs using this mod.</text>
	<text id="ui_enable_reward">Are you sure about enabling Contract Reward Pages?
Enabling Contract Reward Pages will reward you powerful Equip Page after future completion of High Risk Level Reception. Previously accquired Reward Pages will also be given after re-enabling Contract Rewards.</text>
	<text id="ui_ForDemo">Preview</text>
	<text id="ui_Jeaheon_counter">Counter Form</text>
	<text id="ui_PrimeSoul_1">First Page</text>
	<text id="ui_PrimeSoul_2">Second Page</text>
	<text id="Tanya_Brawl_none">None</text>
	<text id="Speed_Furioso">Speed Furioso</text>
	<text id="Enhance_HeavySmoke_Passive">When attacking, if target has Suffocating Haze, deal +{0} damage.
When hit, if the attacker has Suffocating Haze, take {1} less damage.</text>		
	<text id="Zombie_name">Nameless Shell</text>
	<text id="WaltzDecay_text">Take {0} Damage and Stagger Damage at the End of the Scene and Subtract 1 stack
If the character has both Corrosions and the difference between their stacks is less than {1}, they will take no Damage and Stagger Damage from them</text>
	<text id="marked_dice_desc">&lt;color=#FFA226&gt;Yesterday Promise&lt;/color&gt; </text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Conductor">Conductor: At the end of each Scene, set Emotion Level to the highest Emotion Level among all Reverberation Ensemble members.</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Cello">Cello: When using Page with Slash dice, boost all dice of that page maximum value by +2.</text>
 	<text id="Reverberation_Harp">Harp: After successful hit with Blunt die, recover 2 Stagger Resist.</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Drum">Percussion: The third Blunt Die gain +1 Power.</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Horn">Horn: Pierce dice gain +2 Damage.</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Tuba">Tuba: Pierce dice gain +2 Break Damage.</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Trombone">Trombone: Pierce dice gain +1 Power.</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Clarinet">Clarinet: After successful hit with Pierce die, next die gain +1 Power.</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Viola">Viola: After rolling a Slash die, the next Slash die gain +2 minimun value.</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_S_Violin">Second Violin: Slash dice gain +2 Break Damage</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_F_Violin">First Violin: Slash dice gain +2 Damage</text>
	<text id="Reverberation_Organ">Pipe Organ: In a Clash with Blunt die, reduce incoming damage by 2.</text>
</localize>