<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BattleEffectTextRoot xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<effectTextList>
		<BattleEffectText ID="Insanity">
			<Name>Insanity</Name>
			<Desc>Gain 1 stack after inflicting or recieving damage equal to 2% of Max HP</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="NullifyPowerAll">
			<Name>Power Stripped</Name>
			<Desc>Dice are not affected by Power gain or loss</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="Mark">
			<Name>Red Mark</Name>
			<Desc>Target of a Puppet Angelica Librarian</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="AngelicaPuppet">
			<Name>Puppet Strings</Name>
			<Desc>Gain 1 Speed die, The character is controlable.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="TemporyPuppet">
			<Name>Temporary Puppet Strings</Name>
			<Desc>Gain 1 Speed dice; Immortal for the duraction of this Scene.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="CC_Barrier">
			<Name>Sealing Barrier</Name>
			<Desc>Cannot act, Untargetable.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="CrossBurn">
			<Name>Scorched</Name>
			<Desc>Being Hit by The Vermilion Cross will reduce the stack by 1 and make her attack other random Librarian with damage boosed by {0}%</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="TanyaMaster">
			<Name>One Man Army</Name>
			<Desc>If Tanya uses combat pages against the same Librarian 4 times in one Scene, she will “see through” that librarian's attacks;
Next scene, upon clashing with Tanya, she will destroy all dice from that librarian's combat pages.
Librarians that have been seen through this scene: {0}</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="GretaMeat">
			<Name>Fresh Meat</Name>
			<Desc>Can't act. Upon being hit enemies will recover HP equal to damage dealt.
Change resistance to Noraml. Cannot take more Damage than 10% of their max HP in a scene and takes no Stagger Damage.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="HeadDonkey">
			<Name>Heehaw’s Hour to Shine</Name>
			<Desc>Heehaw's Combat Page will be played on the Last Speed die.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="HeadDog">
			<Name>Woof’s Warmup Performance</Name>
			<Desc>Woof's Combat Page will be played on the Last Speed die.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="HeadChicken">
			<Name>Doodle-doo’s Cocky Session</Name>
			<Desc>Doodle-doo's Combat Page will be played on the Last Speed die.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="TrollIndicator">
			<Name>A little Trolling</Name>
			<Desc>At the end of this Scene, the librarian that dealt the most damage will be stupified.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="LibrarianDaze">
			<Name>Stupefied</Name>
			<Desc>Lasts 2 Scenes. Uncontrollable. Upon losing a clash, takes bonus Stagger damage equal to 5% of Max Stagger Resist. If the character is Staggered, this status is removed at the end of the Scene, and the character recovers from Stagger next Scene.</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
		<BattleEffectText ID="CC_Reverberation">
			<Name>Perfect Extraction -- Reverberation Ensemble</Name>
			<Desc>All characters with this passive will receive following bonus:
</Desc>
		</BattleEffectText>
	</effectTextList>
</BattleEffectTextRoot>